<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quizwithfeedback>
  <nextbuttontext>Next</nextbuttontext>
  <submitbuttontext>Submit</submitbuttontext>
  <reviewbuttontext>Review</reviewbuttontext>
  <retakequizbuttontext>Retake</retakequizbuttontext>
  <nextbuttontext>Try Again</nextbuttontext>
  <questioncounttextbegin>Question</questioncounttextbegin>
  <questioncounttextmiddle>of</questioncounttextmiddle>
  <answernothingselectedtext>Please select an answer.</answernothingselectedtext>
  <twoanswerstoofewselected>Select Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoofewselected>
  <twoanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoomanyselected>
  <threeanswerstoofewselected>Select Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoofewselected>
  <threeanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoomanyselected>
  <numberofattempts>Number of attempts: </numberofattempts>
  <numberofquestions>1</numberofquestions>
  <question1>
    <numbercorrect>1</numbercorrect>
    <correctanswer1>4</correctanswer1>
    <numberofansweroptions>4</numberofansweroptions>
    <accessibility>Question 1. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s). The controls for the knowledge check are as follows: To select the first option press 1 on the keyboard, to select the second
      option, press 2, the third 3, the fourth 4, and if there is a fifth 5. To submit your answer choice, select Enter on the keyboard. If you incorrectly answered the question, press Shift-Enter to reset your selections.</accessibility>
    <question>An App Builder at Universal Containers wants to include a new Visualforce page on the mobile navigation menu. What solution can the App Builder recommend for this requirement?</question>
    <option1buttontext>A</option1buttontext>
    <option1text>Add the new Visualforce page to the smart search items section of the navigation menu.</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect. Before you can include Visualforce pages, Lightning pages, or Lightning components in the Salesforce app navigation menu, a new tab must be created for them.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2buttontext>B</option2buttontext>
    <option2text>Move the Visualforce tab to the top of the navigation list.</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Incorrect. Before adjusting the navigation menu, a tab must created for the Visualforce page and then added to the navigation menu.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3buttontext>C</option3buttontext>
    <option3text>Create a new Lightning app tab and include the app in the navigation menu.</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Incorrect. This does not meet the business requirements because a new Lightning app tab is not needed. Only a new Visualforce tab is needs to be added to the navigation menu.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4buttontext>D</option4buttontext>
    <option4text>Create a new Visualforce tab and then add the tab to the navigation menu.</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Correct. Before you can include Visualforce pages, Lightning pages, or Lightning components in the Salesforce app navigation menu, a new tab must be created for them.</option4textexplanation>
  </question1>
</quizwithfeedback>
