<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quizwithfeedback>
  <nextbuttontext>Next</nextbuttontext>
  <submitbuttontext>Submit</submitbuttontext>
  <reviewbuttontext>Review</reviewbuttontext>
  <retakequizbuttontext>Retake</retakequizbuttontext>
  <nextbuttontext>Try Again</nextbuttontext>
  <questioncounttextbegin>Question</questioncounttextbegin>
  <questioncounttextmiddle>of</questioncounttextmiddle>
  <answernothingselectedtext>Please select an answer.</answernothingselectedtext>
  <twoanswerstoofewselected>Select Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoofewselected>
  <twoanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoomanyselected>
  <threeanswerstoofewselected>Select Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoofewselected>
  <threeanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoomanyselected>
  <numberofattempts>Number of attempts: </numberofattempts>
  <numberofquestions>3</numberofquestions>
  <question1>
    <numbercorrect>1</numbercorrect>
    <correctanswer1>2</correctanswer1>
    <numberofansweroptions>4</numberofansweroptions>
    <accessibility>Question 1. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s). The controls for the knowledge check are as follows: To select the first option press 1 on the keyboard, to select the second
      option, press 2, the third 3, the fourth 4, and if there is a fifth 5. To submit your answer choice, select Enter on the keyboard. If you incorrectly answered the question, press Shift-Enter to reset your selections.</accessibility>
    <question>The marketing manager at Universal Containers is sending communication emails out to customers and wants to track the open rates over the next few weeks. They are only sending a small number of emails. What should the App Builder
      recommend to meet these requirements?</question>
    <option1buttontext>A</option1buttontext>
    <option1text>Use a third-party tool and integrate it into Salesforce.</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not the ideal solution as customers can get apps that extend functionality through Salesforce AppExchange.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2buttontext>B</option2buttontext>
    <option2text>Download an app from AppExchange to extend functionality.</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Correct. You can get apps on AppExchange to extend the functionality of the tool. AppExchange is the official Salesforce app marketplace to get applications that meet our security and trust requirements.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3buttontext>C</option3buttontext>
    <option3text>Outsource a contractor to develop a custom app just for this requirement.</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not an ideal solution. The cost and time to develop a custom tool would go beyond the date when the marketing manager would need the tool. Instead, the contractor should consider downloading an app from
      AppExchange to extend functionality.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4buttontext>D</option4buttontext>
    <option4text>Use a third-party platform that meets these requirements.</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not the ideal solution as customers can get apps that extend functionality and use cases through Salesforce AppExchange.</option4textexplanation>
  </question1>
  <question2>
    <numbercorrect>1</numbercorrect>
    <correctanswer1>3</correctanswer1>
    <numberofansweroptions>4</numberofansweroptions>
    <accessibility>Question 2. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s).</accessibility>
    <question>A sales manager from Universal Containers wants to assign leads that come in from their website to queues. What standard process can the App Builder recommend?</question>
    <option1buttontext>A</option1buttontext>
    <option1text>Create an apex class that sorts leads into queues.</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect. The best way to sort leads that come in from a website is to use lead queues to create a lead assignment rule and activate it.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2buttontext>B</option2buttontext>
    <option2text>Create a manual process to sort leads into queues.</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Incorrect. Leads can be automated using a lead assignment rule to sort leads that come in from a website into lead queues. Create a lead assignment rule and activate it.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3buttontext>C</option3buttontext>
    <option3text>Create a lead assignment rule that sorts leads into queues.</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Correct. First, create a lead queue and select a default owner in lead settings for the leads that don’t meet the assignment criteria. Then create a lead assignment rule and activate it.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4buttontext>D</option4buttontext>
    <option4text>Create a default lead owner who sorts leads into queues.</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Incorrect. This will not work because lead owners cannot filter leads into queues. Only lead assignment rules can filter leads based on assignment criteria in a lead assignment rule. The best way to sort leads that come
      in from a website is to use lead queues, create a lead assignment rule and activate it.</option4textexplanation>
  </question2>
  <question3>
    <numbercorrect>1</numbercorrect>
    <correctanswer1>2</correctanswer1>
    <numberofansweroptions>4</numberofansweroptions>
    <accessibility>Question 3. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s).</accessibility>
    <question>In order to delete Opportunities, Universal Containers would like sales reps to submit requests for approval from their sales manager. What can be used to meet these requirements?</question>
    <option1buttontext>A</option1buttontext>
    <option1text>Process Builder with an auto submit for approval action</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect: While Process Builder meets the requirement for the approval scenario, this still leaves the requirement of deleting the opportunities once approved.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2buttontext>B</option2buttontext>
    <option2text>Approval Process with an Apex Trigger</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Correct: An Approval Process to submit the opportunity for delete and a trigger to delete the Opportunity once approved.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3buttontext>C</option3buttontext>
    <option3text>Two-step Approval Process</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Incorrect: A two-step approval process is not needed.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4buttontext>D</option4buttontext>
    <option4text>Approval Process with Time-Dependent Workflow action</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Incorrect: A time-dependent workflow action does not have the capability to delete an Opportunity.</option4textexplanation>
  </question3>
</quizwithfeedback>
