<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<quizwithfeedback>
  <nextbuttontext>Next</nextbuttontext>
  <submitbuttontext>Submit</submitbuttontext>
  <reviewbuttontext>Review</reviewbuttontext>
  <retakequizbuttontext>Retake</retakequizbuttontext>
  <nextbuttontext>Try Again</nextbuttontext>
  <questioncounttext>Question {0} of {1}</questioncounttext>
  <answernothingselectedtext>Please select an answer.</answernothingselectedtext>
  <twoanswerstoofewselected>Select Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoofewselected>
  <twoanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Two (2) Answers</twoanswerstoomanyselected>
  <threeanswerstoofewselected>Select Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoofewselected>
  <threeanswerstoomanyselected>Select Only Three (3) Answers</threeanswerstoomanyselected>
  <numberofattempts>Number of attempts: </numberofattempts>
  <question1>
    <accessibility>Question 1. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s). The controls for the knowledge check are as follows: To select the first option press 1 on the keyboard, to select the second
      option, press 2, the third 3, the fourth 4, and if there is a fifth 5. To submit your answer choice, select Enter on the keyboard. If you incorrectly answered the question, press Shift-Enter to reset your selections.</accessibility>
    <question>The Sales team wants to enter in the key fields on an account. They would also like to ensure the fields are easily accessible in the mobile app. Which standard Lightning component can the App Builder recommend?</question>
    <option1text>Accordion component</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect. The accordion component organizes your components into collapsible sections. This does not meet the business requirement.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2text>Record Detail component</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Incorrect. The Record Detail component displays fields and sections from the page layout associated with the object. Limiting fields on the page layout does not meet the business requirement.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3text>Highlights Panel</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Correct. The Highlights Panel component displays key record fields and the fields that appear in the highlights panel come from the compact layout assigned to the object.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4text>Rich Text component</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Incorrect. Use the Rich Text component to add text and simple HTML markup to your Lightning page. This does not meet the business requirement.</option4textexplanation>
  </question1>
  <question2>
    <accessibility>Question 2. This question has 4 possible answer(s) to chose from. The question has 1 correct answer(s).</accessibility>
    <question>An App Builder at Universal Containers is creating a new Lightning app for the sales team. What considerations should the App Builder take to ensure the navigation menu is efficient?</question>
    <option1text>Add all tabs for the navigation menu and let users remove what they don’t use.</option1text>
    <option1textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not possible as users cannot remove tabs from apps. Users can add and customize their navigation menu up to 50 items.</option1textexplanation>
    <option2text>Limit the number of tabs selected for the navigation menu to a small number.</option2text>
    <option2textexplanation>Correct. Users can’t remove tabs, only add. If the development team adds 20 items for the app, then users can only add 30 more items. Users can add and customize their navigation menu up to 50 items.</option2textexplanation>
    <option3text>Only add Chatter, Reports, and Dashboards. Let users customize and make the app what they need.</option3text>
    <option3textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not efficient for users. The team needs to add the items ideal for the specific app’s purpose, but keep the number items to a reasonable amount. Users can add and customize their navigation menu up to
      50 items. Then cannot take away but only add items.</option3textexplanation>
    <option4text>Create a custom homepage for users.</option4text>
    <option4textexplanation>Incorrect. This is not efficient for users. The team needs to add the items ideal for the specific app’s purpose, but keep the number items to a reasonable amount. Users can add and customize their navigation menu up to
      50 items.</option4textexplanation>
  </question2>
</quizwithfeedback>
